birthdaymessages.net 2016-06-12

# Privacy Policy

Advertisement

* * *

[ **Home**](http://www.birthdaymessages.net/) > **Privacy Policy**

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use BirthdayMessages.net, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope that this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

BirthdayMessages.net strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting the privacy of our customers, consumers and online visitors on our website.

 **Personal Information**  

BirthdayMessages.net collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include your name, email address, postal address and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.  

 **Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**  

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize any page on this site or register for any of our site's services, a cookie enables BirthdayMessages.net to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your web browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of using the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We also allow certain third-party companies to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to BirthdayMessages.net and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

 **Non-Personal Information**  

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.  

 **How You Can Correct or Remove Information**  

We have provided this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our [Contact Me](http://www.birthdaymessages.net/contact-me.html) page.  

 **Updates and Effective Date**  

BirthdayMessages.net reserves the right to make changes to this policy. If there is a material change to our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy, so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

 **Agreeing to Terms**  

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
